Amanda Seales. Because, I, you know,
y'all always got me defending Amanda.
Why y'all always got me defending
Amanda?
Like, I don't know why, you know, y'all
always got me defending Amanda. Okay,
so,
Amanda posted this.
Okay?
Tiffany Haddish Netflix doc about not
being on the Insecure tour. And there's
a bunch of comments
where people are asking her about it.
>> It's fine.
It's fine.
Derrick!
>> I thought this was hilarious.
I thought it was funny.
I thought it was funny. I didn't think
I didn't like take this seriously. Like,
because then the topic becomes like,
"Girl, of course you're not invited."
It's like, well, it's not really a
question of being invited. It's making
fun of the fact that I'm not invited.
It's not like me saying I don't know
why.
>> [laughter]
>> I thought it was hilarious. I'm sorry.
It's fine. It's fine.
It's fine.
>> [laughter]
>> I thought it was funny. So, that I
don't, you know, but somebody was like,
"Really, Baddie, you didn't think
everybody was going to go to hell on
Amanda about any and everything she does
that goes viral?" And yeah. These are
some of the comments. And And when I
talk about like just this unnecessary
hate that y'all have towards people,
I get it. I get not liking people for
things that they do and and and takes
that they have. Trust me. I block a lot
of [ __ ] cuz y'all say [ __ ] that
I'm just like, "Yeah, I can't get jiggy
with you at all if you think like that.
I don't know what's wrong with you." Uh
but I can't be around you. You know what
I'm saying? I do that often.
We going to run through
some of those people.
Okay? Because, uh you know, we got to
talk about some of you weird ass black
women on the internet, you know? For all
of For all of y'all that's always
talking about how much I hate these
[ __ ] and it's always a man's fault.
Where are you now, hoe?
Uh.
Though I was not invited to participate
in the reunion tour, I am proud of my
role in the iconic show. Had to
improvise with the hair here, but the
essence of Tiff is still there. And it
was. And And this was just funny and it
wasn't a big deal.
The first comment. Um the least
memorable character that I could have
done without. Nasty bougie light-skinned
who is feeling it and probably off
camera, too. I'm sorry, Amanda. I love
your intelligence, though.
Girl, [ __ ] you.
I I act like you not trying to play the
[ __ ] out somebody by saying that their
character was the least memorable
character of all. Her character was not
the least memorable character of all.
Derek is the least memorable character
of all.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay? One of them other [ __ ] that
Issa [ __ ] that I can't remember.
Uh
Another person said, "I get your point,
but this post feels a little troll-like,
especially if you want to be included in
receiving an apology. I may just have
chilled. People have to come to terms
with their wrong on their own time since
you can't force it, but love Tiffany." I
See, do you see all of what people are
putting on to this situation simply
because she made a joke about it? Do you
see like And that would be I would be
sitting up there reading that [ __ ] and
it would be pissing me off because y'all
are wrong, but y'all think y'all got it.
Like y'all think y'all have figured it
out.
Some Oh my god. Girl, all of this All of
this?
Girl, just do a review on Tik Tok. Do a
video. Why are you in somebody's
comments with all of this? Y'all, look
at this. Girl, not all of this.
All of this?
Look.
I Listen, I appreciate engagement. I
love y'all for real, but if you feel
like you got to do a bullet-pointed
review of the [ __ ] show,
then I'm really going to need for you to
go ahead and make a video about it. I'm
going to need for you to to respond with
a video. Okay, make a video and tag
people. But don't don't don't come in
nobody comments writing no [ __ ]
no dissertation in the comments, [ __ ]
Writing no article in the comments.
Like seriously, I wouldn't hang with
nobody at my job, but I'm at every
potluck and promotion. This is business
and excluding her isn't professional.
And for sake of fanfare, why wouldn't
you give the full access and
transparency just like I wouldn't have
watched a Fresh Prince reunion without
Aunt Viv or That's So Raven reunion
without Orlando Brown. To leave out
Amanda, I wasn't interested. It fell
short without including her voice, her
presence, and the experience of her
character.
Low-key, I kind of like agree and then I
disagree because, you know, um shout-out
to Donny Morgan. She was saying like
that's the that's the um plus about
having your own [ __ ] is that you don't
have to include people that you don't
want to include.
And I get that, okay? And I one of them
people that have totally, you know, not
totally, but child, I'm about 75% good
with the fact that my authenticity and
me not bending on my opinion for the
validation of celebrities is probably a
reason why I'm kind of kept on the
outskirts the way I am even though I'm
one of them people that you can invite
to a party and I ain't going to say
[ __ ]
>> [laughter]
>> But that's cool though cuz sometimes I
don't want to be invited to some of them
parties.
You know what I'm saying?
But I you know, I be liking all of the
black you know, when the black girls be
doing [ __ ] I be like, you know, and
some of them cool ass black dudes that I
like, you know, like them Jam podcast
kids and and and De'ante and the people,
you know, like I [ __ ] with them. You
know what I mean? I like them. Uh but
outside of that like no, I'm I'm not
that I'm not super, you know, wanting to
to included like that in in [ __ ] that
makes me feel I don't know unsafe. But I
I do agree with this comment because I
do feel like if it's about the fandom,
if it's about the show, then your
feelings doesn't really need to be a
part of why. I also feel like just the
fact that y'all possibly could have had
a disagreement
like on stage. I'm guessing this is like
a situation where y'all go from city to
city and come out on stage and talk
about the show and talk about the
characters and all of that type of
stuff. I feel like the back and forth
that could possibly happen with Amanda
on stage would make [ __ ] go viral for
sure.
Um and that's good for business. So I do
feel like it would have been better if
Amanda was there. However, do I truly
give a [ __ ] No.
But I do miss the days where
you know, we didn't know. Like back in
the day, celebrities could be beefed the
[ __ ] out behind the scenes. [ __ ] we
didn't know. They're standing next to
each other taking pictures, arm around
each other.
>> [laughter]
>> Beefed the [ __ ] out and we would have
never known.
[ __ ] standing next to each
other smiling and hugging and [ __ ] while
saying, "Get your [ __ ] hands off me,
[ __ ] I hate you."
>> [laughter]
>> Girl.
Um
So yeah, I I I definitely miss the days
of us being able to like put that [ __ ]
to the side so that you know, a fan
experience could be had without people
being left out. Um
No, you did your first time seeing the
video you thought Amanda said something
crazy. Yeah, I I don't I feel like
everybody's tripping.
>> [laughter]
>> I think people are like imposing a lot
of emotion onto what she did. When
sometimes when you as a Gemini that
easily accept [ __ ] sometimes like you
accept what things are, you don't try to
change it, you don't try to manipulate
it and you know, flip it into a [ __ ]
pretzel so it can fit into a narrative
that makes me feel comfortable. I don't
do that type of [ __ ] I just accept
things for what they are because then I
can just move appropriately. That saves
me a lot of time and stress as far as
I'm concerned. I've learned that in this
life, okay? And so, just because you can
acknowledge something, just because you
can see something, just because you can
make a joke about something, doesn't
mean some deep feeling is held on to it
like that. Like I made the joke. It's
fine though. Like we don't get along.
I'm not included. It sucks. I would have
liked to be included, but I'mma make a
joke about it because people already
asking me about it. But once I make the
joke and I get the, you know, the laugh
off of it, then it kind of diffuses the
situation when you can laugh about
something. I think it's so funny how
when it be [ __ ] that you shouldn't be
laughing about, like assaulting kids,
assaulting women, rape, y'all want to
fight about how [ __ ] is just a joke.
When it's something like this that's
really not even that [ __ ] serious,
now all of a sudden everybody want to
terrify the [ __ ] over over a trend on
the internet.
Um and and that's another thing. Issa,
you know, everybody wants to act like
Amanda is the only one with a
somewhat problematic personality.
I love Issa and I always have uh ever
since YouTube days. You know what I'm
saying? Like I I was one of the content
creators that really supported YouTubers
that were creating series content. Okay?
Between Issa and Awkward Black Girl and
Black and Sexy TV and the LGBTQ ones
that were doing it between women and uh
um
Channing and all of them.
Girl. [laughter]
That was Channing show. And then when
y'all changed Channing, I was like, I
don't know what y'all want me to do with
this. You can't change out the Channing.
Like it's Channing's show. Like it's all
y'all show cuz all y'all was cute,
right? All of the studs was on um
Studville TV.
Girl, I miss me some Studville TV. The
the shows in that era of YouTube were
just so great. I wish I had popped more
back then. I don't I mean, I was still
working at the news station, but I wish
I had blew up more back then. I have
I've always had my consistent like
audience over the years, like a you
know, a consistent growth over the
years, but I really wish I had popped a
little harder during that time. But, I
still have like, you know,
mutual relationships with a lot of
people that used to work on those shows.
Shoutout to Janine, Auntie Neen, who now
is on um
TikTok and Instagram, and her social
media platform is showcasing black
uh black fashion.
All the black fashion that she has, you
know what I'm saying? So, I love that.
Uh Chef Julian is on Tubi now. Oh my
god, Chef Julian's on Tubi?
And Studville TV laughing my butt off.
Girl, you know Listen, and the Between
Women theme song plays in my head
forever, and I'm honestly kind of
offended by the fact that I have never
run into Look Alive. After all of these
years, I have never ran into that girl,
not in New Well, not before Katrina, and
you know, after the show and all of
that. I'm always surprised when it's
like gay people that grew up in New
Orleans, and I have never seen, met
them. God, I don't know why. Like, New
Orleans New Orleans is not that [ __ ]
small, but it is.
Either way, y'all, I feel like
everybody, you know, there is a level of
nostalgia that they all have for me.
Because back then, Amanda was on
YouTube, and Amanda had this really,
really funny like sketch comedy show
that she used to do. And honestly, I I
always say I love that.
I think uh Jamie works with her
sometimes, but I always say that I
really loved when Amanda had that show,
that sketch comedy show. Uh I forgot
what it was called, but it also had a
really good theme song, you know what I
mean?
Uh but yeah, I I tend to be very
forgiving to black women that may be
problematic, right? But, they haven't
actually hurt anybody. I tend to be
forgiving of them. Amanda is somebody
that I think is probably a [ __ ] to
people, but I'm more forgiving of that.
Because that to me that's not as serious
as some of the [ __ ] y'all be trying to
let slide out here.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, y'all try to let too much [ __ ]
slide. But, when it comes to, you know,
Amanda, Amanda say something. It ain't
even that [ __ ] serious, okay? One of
the main things that she did that pissed
everybody off was when the [ __ ] happened
with Cheyenne Bryant, and that's as of
recent. She didn't really come out to
admonish Cheyenne Bryant while also
toting, um, you know, her intellectual
prowess. Like, Amanda is always toting
her intellectual prowess, girl. And so,
why somebody lying about having a
[ __ ] doctorate is not enough for you
to have pause, right? I still feel that
way.
Does that mean I throw Amanda away every
time we have one of these moments? No,
okay? I just don't.
Speaking of Cheyenne, she decided to
join the exact same trend that Amanda
Seales did. When Netflix does a
documentary on Dr. Cheyenne Bryant,
episode one will ask, is she really a
doctor? Episodes two through 10 will
investigate why a complete jealous
envious haters tried to prove she
wasn't. Girl, you would never get no 10
episodes on no documentary on Netflix.
YouTube, maybe.
Netflix, I don't even Netflix is not
doing three You're a one episode person
on a show that does a series on people
that lied about being doctors.
Girl.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Is this my camera? Oh, is this my
camera?
Oh, this is my camera?
This is how you are really supposed to
do that.
Let's play the music. Let's play the
music. Okay, we're going to play the
music then we going to we going to try
this. This is what she really should
have did.
This is the diploma.
>> [music]
>> Like
[ __ ] don't get a piece of clothing.
Go get the paperwork, okay?
I I was looking around to see if my
diploma was down here, but I think my I
mean up here, but my diploma I think is
downstairs, okay? Child
I look I'm about to go find my my
college diploma, [ __ ] to pull up and
be like, "No, [ __ ] what you was really
supposed to do was sit down with the
diploma and place it in front of the
camera.
That's That's a flex. You can go get
these little these little uniforms that
you got on from anywhere, [ __ ] The
[ __ ]
These hoes not even doing it right.
Okay?
Make me go get
Make me go get my [ __ ] college
diploma, okay?
Or the high school one. I have them
both.
I'm not one of them people that leave
all their paperwork with their mama. I'm
an adult.
I have my own paperwork.
I have my own house.
Okay?
The [ __ ] out of here with that [ __ ]
>> [screaming]
>> Oh my god, they pulled it up. They
pulled it up, y'all. They pulled it up
on Amazon.
Because you have to get these for the
graduation. So, there of course there're
going to be somewhere that you can
purchase them.
That is hilarious.
Oh my god. The tickle that just gave me.
Uh, let's move on, you guys.